#72 MOTTA TRACE,

TABAQUITE.

May 24th 2017

Dear Sir or Madam:

I am seeking employment in your organization. I completed 1 year and a half of a **BA** in **English** at the **University of the Southern Caribbean, Maracas, St Joseph** which I discontinued, to do my two year certificate course in **Physical Education at the University of the West Indies (Open Campus)** part time at which I am now a successful graduate. I enclose my resume and hope that you may consider me to become part of your organization.

I have a desire to pursue a career in Physical Education/Administrative/Secretarial work. This is because of my involvement my areas of studies and my previous and present work experience. However I am willing to learn and accept any opening that there may be.

As an employee of your organization, I would work at my full potential to meet deadlines and produce the results that is needed for today's competitive environment.

I do hope you look upon my resume with favour and look forward to you accepting me into your organization. Thank you for your consideration.

Respectfully yours,

Verlea Duprey

## HOME ADDRESS: #72 MOTTA TRACE, TABAQUITE.

### PHONE 377-8648 E-MAIL verleeduprey@yahoo.com

### **VERLEA DUPREY**

## PERSONAL

**GENDER** Female

**Date of Birth** 4<sup>th</sup> November 1989

Marital Status Single

**Nationality** Trinidadian

#### OBJECTIVE\_

To apply the knowledge and the skills I have developed in an organization that supports student development and growth.

## EDUCATION\_

# (2008-2010) The University Of The West Indies: Certificate in Physical Education 2<sup>nd</sup> Year Final Semester

Observation and Analysis in Physical Education **B** 

Statistical Evaluation and Measurement in Phys Ed B

# (2008-2010) The University Of The West Indies: Certificate in Physical Education 2<sup>nd</sup> Year 2<sup>nd</sup> Semester

Anatomy and Physiology B

Adapted Physical Education **B** 

### Curriculum and Planning in Phys Ed C

# (2008-2010) The University Of The West Indies: Certificate in Physical Education 2<sup>nd</sup> Year 1<sup>st</sup> Semester

Anatomy and Physiology B

Organization and Administration of Physical Education C

Motor Learning and Skill Performances C

# COURSES COMPLETED (PASSED ALL) 1st Semester September 2008

- . Language Skills and Communication **B**+
- . Fundamentals and Elements of Physical Education  ${f Ao}$
- . Principles and Philosophy of Physical Education **Bo**

# COURSES COMPLETED (PASSED ALL) 2<sup>nd</sup> Semester January 2009

- . Methods and Materials C+
- . Intro to Guidance and Counseling. B-
- . History and foundations of Physical Education. Ao

# COURSES COMPLETED 3rd Semester May-July 2009

- . Nutrition and Community Health A
- . Care and Prevention in Sports Related Injuries C

#### PRACTICALS COMPLETED: (PASSED ALL)

- . Hockey Ao
- . Dance B-
- . Educational Gymnastics A+
- . Football A-

- . Athletics B
- . Swimming C

## PRACTICALS COMPLETED: (PASSED ALL)

- . Volleyball B
- . Tennis A
- . Basketball A
- . Cricket A

# 2007-2008 University of the Southern Caribbean, Maracas, St Joseph

# **BA** English

Courses Completed: B.A. English: Semester I (PASSED ALL)

- . God and Human Life C-
- . Basic Spanish C-
- . English Composition 1 B-
- . A literary Experience A
- . Communication Skills A

# Courses Completed: B.A. English Semester II (PASSED ALL)

- . Principles of Sociology B
- . World Civilization B-

# Courses Completed B.A. English 2<sup>nd</sup> Year Semester I (PASSED ALL)

- . Introduction to Rhetoric C
- . Jesus in His Time and Ours B

# 2001-2006 Tabaquite Composite Secondary School

# Emmanuel Junction,

# Tabaquite.

# 2006-2007 School of Modern Business (Private) General Proficiency

# $2010 \ \textbf{Chaguanas North Secondary School (Private) General Proficiency}$

Ordinary Level	GRADE
. CXC English	I
. CXC Office Administration	III
. CXC Type Writing	III
. CXC Social Studies	III
. CXC Principles of Business	III
. CXC Integrated Science	III

#### **Achievements**

- . I made the Trinidad and Tobago Women's Football League (TTWOLF)All Star Team for 2012
- . In August of 2000, I did the computer literacy course with the National Energy Skills Center and Ministry of Education at the Tabaquite Composite Secondary School.
- In September 14<sup>th</sup> 2007 to September 24<sup>th</sup> 2007, I went on the Trinidad and Tobago Football Federation Course for Football Coaching, where I have successfully achieved my coaching certificate. I doing this I am now a Trinidad and Tobago certified football coach.
- . In April 2008, I went on the Trinidad and Tobago referee's association recruitment course where I successfully passed the exam. Thus meaning, I am now a member of The Trinidad and Tobago Referees Association.
- .I was named most promising referee by the Trinidad and Tobago Referee's Association (central zone) for the year 2008.
- . Secondary School Football League SSFL Represented Tabaquite Composite School playing football on the School Girls Championship team, from Form one to Form three.
- . On June  $14^{th}$  2008, I went to Canada with my club, Waterloo Institute of Soccer players as both a coach and a player on Waterloo Minor Soccer club Canada  $34^{th}$  invitational soccer tournament where I achieved player recognition.
- . On May  $20^{th}$ - $29^{th}$ , I proudly represented the University of the West Indies, St Augustine in the UWI Inter Campus games 2009 in the discipline of football where we placed  $2^{nd}$ .
- . I passed my referees fitness test for the year 2009 at which I now have the chance to be promoted to refereeing at the Super and pro league in Trinidad and Tobago.
- . In 2009 I was highlighted on the nation's television (sports news) because of my great skills and performance in football, I lead my football club to victory in the Trinidad and Tobago Women's league football big 4 competition which put me in the spotlight and I was given the sports play of the day on Monday  $24^{th}$  August 2009 on CCN TV6.

- . I am one of the founders/secretary/female coach of the **Arima Giants WFC** which was established in 2006 and was able to put all heads together as one and enter the Trinidad and Tobago Women's League football for the 1<sup>st</sup> time in 2010 at which we placed 2<sup>nd</sup> in the first division.
- . I am also one of the Founders/Secretary/coach of the Todds Road Soccer Clinic which was established in the year 2012 to present.
- . In May 2010 I took a try at the Scholastic Aptitude Tests (SATs) and gained an 1100.
- . I was named most valuable player for my club in 2010 after being the top goal scorer in the TT Women's League Football after scoring 12 goals in 6 matches.
- . In 2010 I completed my **two year part time certificate in Physical Education at the UWI Open Campus**
- . As an employee of the Ministry of Sport and Youth Affairs for the year of employment as a Sport Development Officer I ran four programs.

#### 2010

- -The 1st ever all female futsal tournament which was well attended
- Trinidad and Tobago Football Refereeing Course. (East and Central Zones)

#### 2011

1st ever Todd's Road Community Sports Festival

- Arima/Eldorado Soccer Development Clinic for females only in Primary Schools

## **Work Experience**

- . I am currently employed by the National Maintainence and Security Services Limited (MTS) as a permanent Security Officer.
- . In 2015-2016 I was employed by the National Training Agency as a Level 2 on the Job Trainee (OJT) at the Tabaquite RC Primary School as **Continuous Assessment Component (CAC)**
- . I was an office clerk/cashier/data entry clerk at Caparo Shoprite Grocery Limited for the period November 2013-May 2014.
- . In 2013 I was the head football coach of the Tabaquite Secondary School boys Under 16 team, the Assistant coach of the Championship Boys Football Team, the assistant coach of the Arima North Secondary School Girl Championship Football Team and the Head Coach of the Tabaquite Secondary School Girls Football team for the 2013 Secondary School Football League (SSFL)
- . I was employed at the Ministry of Sport and Youth Affairs on a 2 year contract as a Sport Development Officer. November 2010-May 2012

I was employed at DirecOne as a Telephone Operator, in the Bmobile Customer Service Representative department.

I am employed (part time) at the Arima Senior Comprehensive School, as the head female coach of the Under 15 female football team. I have been employed there for the past 2 years.

I was employed at the Waterloo Institute of Soccer players as the specialized coach of the female team, where I took certain players and developed them in a certain area, example striking. Also I served as an assistant coach at the institute. I was employed by this institute for the 1 year.

I am a referee, so this would also be part of my work experience because it takes someone with dedication and a high level of fitness to fit the requirements for the field pf play.

I was employed at the Chaguanas Borough Corporation, at which I was a Data Entry Clerk/Clerical Staff.

During the summer vacation (2008), I worked as a coach in the sports camps which were held in various communities throughout **Trinidad and Tobago**, in collaboration with **THE MINISTRY OF SPORTS AND YOUTH AFFAIRS, THE SPORTT COMPANY AND THE TOBAGO HOUSE OF ASSEMBLY.** I worked in Presentation College Chaguanas.

#### **HOBBIES**

Playing Football, Coaching, Cycling, Sprinting, Cricket, Surfing the Internet, Reading and Writing.

#### REFERENCES

Mr Elton Santana

#69 Main Road Tabaquite

Retired Teacher

Manager of the Tabaquite Secondary School male football Teams

Contact: 689-8878

Mrs Ann Bahadoorsingh

Diaz Road Tabaquite

Principal of the Tabaquite Rc Primary School

Contact: 347-9970